<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Mark Edosa</title>
    <link>https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Mark Edosa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Mark Edosa</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with git</title>
      <link>https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/git/</guid>
      <description>Git is a version control system (VCS) that is very useful for tracking content in files.
Description It has three areas:
 The working directory (working tree) - contains your files The staging area (or index) - a temporary storage for changes your files the repository - a somewhat permanent store for your files  The workflow:
 Initialize an empty git repository if it&amp;rsquo;s a new project or clone an existing repository Make changes to the content of files / create new files Add files to the index Commit the changes to the local repository And Optionally push to a remote repository hosted via sites such as github, bitbucket etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with NPM</title>
      <link>https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/npm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maqui7295.github.io/tutorial/npm/</guid>
      <description>Introduction NPM or node package manager is one of tool for managing dependencies of javascript or Nodejs projects.
Typical workflow of an npm project git clone repo cd directory npm i npm start npm test  Getting help npm -h npm install -h npm help &amp;lt;command&amp;gt; # opens browser to the official help page e.g. npm help install npm help-search &amp;lt;list of words&amp;gt; e.g npm help-search remove npm api-help prune npm info pkg  Setting default configuration npm set init-author-name &amp;quot;name of author&amp;quot; npm set init-license &amp;quot;name of author&amp;quot; npm get init-author-name # delete a config npm config delete init-author-name   ls ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>